{
    "identification": [
        {
            "question":"It is a concrete model of how a system will appear or behave, and usually depict the user interface.",
            "answer":"prototype"
        },

        {
            "question":"It is a non-functional user interface layout that uses actual GUI components and  validates UI design.",
            "answer":"Mockup"
        },

        {
            "question":"Its main goal is to build a very robust prototype in a structured manner and constantly refine it",
            "answer":"Evolutionary prototyping"
        },

        {
            "question":"It is the process of applying various techniques and principles for the purpose of defining a device, process or system in sufficient detail to permit its physical realization.",
            "answer":"Design"
        },

        {
            "question":"It refers to the iterative process through which requirements are translated into a “blueprint” for building software.",
            "answer":"Software Design"
        },

        {
            "question":"It establishes a basic structural framework that identifies the major components of a system and the communication among these components.",
            "answer":"Architectural Design"
        },

        {
            "question":"It leads to the accurate specification of requirements, and the construction of a valid and useable system from the users' perspective via conventional software development models",
            "answer":"Throwaway prototyping"
        },

        {
            "question":"It consists of a central data store and a set of independent components that access the data store.",
            "answer":"Repository"
        },

        {
            "question":"This Architectural Style's system is organized as a set of services and associated servers and clients that access and use these services.",
            "answer":"Client-server"
        },

        {
            "question":"It exploits diverse connectivity between participants in a network and the cumulative bandwidth of the network participants.",
            "answer":"Peer-to-peer"
        },

        {
            "question":"These are techniques by which mathematical problems are formulated so that they can be solved with arithmetic operations.",
            "answer":"Numerical methods"
        
        },

        {
            "question":"It refers to how closely a computed or measured value agrees with the true value.",
            "answer":"Accuracy"
        
        },

        {
            "question":"It is a type of incremental search method in which the interval is always divided in half.",
            "answer":"Bolzano's method"
        
        },

        {
            "question":"This is the discrepancy introduced by the fact that numerical methods may employ approximations to represent exact mathematical operations and quantities.",
            "answer":"Transaction error"
        
        },

        {
            "question":"A kind of error that is not directly connected with numerical methods.",
            "answer":"Formulation error"
        
        },

        {
            "question":"When computer programs are divided into small subprograms which can be developed and tested separately then we are doing an approach called.",
            "answer":"Modular programming"
        
        },

        {
            "question":"This software is produced by Microsoft, Inc. that allows the user to enter and perform calculations on rows and columns of data",
            "answer":"Excel"
        
        },

        {
            "question":"It refers to how closely individuals computed or measured agree with each other.",
            "answer":"Precision"
        
        },

        {
            "question":"It refers to the systematic deviation from the truth.",
            "answer":"Inaccuracy"
        
        },

        {
            "question":"It refers to the magnitude of the scatter of the approximate values",
            "answer":"Imprecision"
        
        }


       
    ]
}